yfsmagazine.com 2019-07-12

# Privacy — YFS Magazine

When you read YFS Magazine, you trust us with your information. We are committed to keeping that trust. That starts with helping you understand our privacy practices.

**Last Modified:** May 25, 2018  
**Effective Date:** May 25, 2018

This policy describes the information we collect, how it is used and shared, and your choices regarding this information. YFS Magazine is committed to protecting the privacy of its users. The following outlines our privacy and data protection policy.

Third party partners of YFS Magazine and other websites you may access via YFS Magazine have different privacy policies and are not subject to this privacy policy. We recommend that you read the privacy statement of each such website to find out how they protect your personal information.

## Collection and Use of User Details

When you register at YFS Magazine or subscribe to any of our email newsletters, we may collect personal details about you. Personal information such as your name, address and email address is collected via YFS Magazine’s registration forms.

When you visit the site, we also collect web site usage information and information about your computer and internet connection, including your computer’s IP address, the type and version of browser and operating system you use, your internet domain and, if you arrived at YFS Magazine via a link from another website, the URL of the linking page.

We use this information to:

  * personalize the content and advertising you will see based on your personal characteristics or preferences
  * notify you of relevant new products and features on YFS Magazine (if you opt in to receiving such information)
  * notify you of promotions from YFS Magazine and from partner companies (if you opt in to receiving such information)
  * allow reputable third parties to send you information (again, if you opt in to receiving such information)
  * ensure, as far as is practical, that our site is compatible with the browsers and operating systems used by most of our visitors

We also use the information for in-house research to:

  * improve our understanding of customer needs in developing YFS Magazine
  * build marketing profiles
  * aid strategic development
  * manage our relationship with advertisers

The results of all such research and analysis will be presented as anonymous or aggregated information and will not reveal any personal facts about individual customers.

## User Choices

The registration form may provide you with a series of choices regarding promotional activity and other forms of communication with you. If you want to be kept informed of YFS Magazine products and offers, as well as technical or functional developments related to our website and online services, then you should tick the relevant opt-in box.If you wish, we will occasionally allow other similar, reputable organizations to contact you. If you wish to hear from these companies, please tick the appropriate box on the registration form.

## Cookies

A cookie is a small file which is placed on the user’s hard drive during a YFS Magazine visit. This file allows the user to move quickly and easily around our site. It is used to identify returning users and to identify subscribers and registrants (a registrant – and subscriber – will have the cookie linked to their email address as a way of identifying them). We also use a cookie to track a user’s sessions. We use this information to find out what site features are most popular so that we can develop YFS Magazine in the light of our analysis of people’s usage. We also use cookies and the information we collect to show you relevant content and advertising. You can delete cookies from your hard drive at any time. Further information on the use of cookies can be found at: http://www.cookiecentral.com.

## Emails

YFS Magazine uses reputable third parties to deliver the emails you will receive from our site if you subscribe to our email newsletters or have chosen to receive information about YFS Magazine products and offers. These third parties use unique identifiers and invisible images (often called “pixel tags” or “clear GIFs”) to perform message open sensing, message format sensing, and click-through sensing on behalf of YFS Magazine in order to bring you more relevant information. Content and some ad services in these emails are provided by YFS Magazine or a third-party ad server.

## Ads

“We use a third-party advertising company to serve ads when you visit our Web site. This company may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visit to this Web site in order to provide advertisements about goods and services that may be of interest to you. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique “cookie” on your browser.

## Security Policy

YFS Magazine has appropriate measures in place to ensure that users’ personal details are not misused, accidentally destroyed, lost or altered within the YFS Magazine server environment.

## Transfer of Personal Data Overseas

Given that the Internet is a global environment, using the Internet to collect and process personal data necessarily involves the transmission of data on an international basis. Therefore, by browsing YFS Magazine and communicating electronically with us, you acknowledge and agree to our processing of personal data in this way.

## Changes to this statement

Due to changes in legislation and best practice or enhancements to functionality and content on YFS Magazine we may make changes to our privacy policy and will reflect those changes in this statement, so you should check here from time to time.
